僅供學習 禁止用于任何商業盈利行為
更多影視更新請登陸www.YYeTs.com
翻譯 草草   Reginamoon   米蘇   后期 灰灰是菇涼
校對 米蘇   時間軸 憑陵新月   旅行的木訥   總監 米蘇
憶往昔
快帶你弟弟出去
Take your brother outside as fast as you can!
快走啊  迪恩
Now, Dean! Go!
你還記得什么
What else do you remember?
沒什么了  我當時還是個孩子
Nothing. I was a kid, all right?
最重要的是
And most important --
照顧好薩姆
Watch out for Sammy.
照顧你  是我的職責
Watching out for you -- it's kinda who I am.
我有個哥哥
I got this brother, right?
他總說他會照顧我
And he's always telling me how he's gonna watch out for me.
快吃吧
Now eat your dinner.
別忘了吃蔬菜
Don't forget your vegetables.
你怎么可以認為我會把任何事看得比你還重
Don't you dare think that there is anything that I would put in front of you!
薩姆受傷了  他傷得很重
Sammy's hurt. He's hurt real bad.
我會在治愈自己的同時治愈薩姆
I heal Sam while healing myself.
我每次使用能力  就會變得虛弱
Every time I use my power, it weakens me.
你經歷了兩道測試
You went through the trials.
我只是覺得你還是悠著點比較好
I just think it's better if you took it easy,
別好像是...
you know, and didn't act like you were --
被天使附身的樣子
Possessed by an angel.
如今
等等
Aah! Wait up!
快點  他就在后面
Hurry! He's right behind us.
紐約州  赫利維爾
快點
Come on, come on!
Hurry!
快走  門是開的
Go, go, go -- it's open!
行了  伙計們
Come on, guys.
捉迷藏的時候不許進谷倉
The barn is a no-fly zone during hide-and-go-seek.
孩子們
Boys?
出來啊  你們這些二貨
Come on, you delinquents.
該上床了
Time for bed!
行了  游戲結束了  孩子們
All right! Game is over, boys!
出來吧  10分鐘前就熄燈了
Let's bring it in! Lights out was 10 minutes ago!
你們這些小混蛋
You little bastards.
好吧  我要...
Okay, I'm gonna...
我數到十
You got till the count of 10,
你們再不出來我要抽你們了
and you'd better come out or the belt's coming off!
一
1...
真是的
Come on!
孩子們
Boys?
行了
Come on!
這可不是鬧著玩的
This isn't funny.
兇鬼惡靈
第九季 第七集
壞孩子
迪恩
Dean?
凱文
Kevin?
神奇的奧茲
喂
Hello?
抱歉  這兒沒有什么D狗
I'm sorry, there's no, uh -- there's no dee-dawg, uh...
我來吧
I got it. I got it.
桑尼  什么事
Sonny, hey. So, what's up?
好
Okay.
好的  等著我  我盡快趕到
All right. Yeah, just sit tight. I'll be there as soon as I can.
好
Yeah.
怎么回事啊  D狗
So, what was that all about, dee-dawg?
記得我們小時候在紐約州北部過的那個春天嗎
You remember when we were kids that spring in upstate New York?
爸爸去獵殺法國狼人了
Dad was on a rugaru hunt.
我們就去...
We, uh -- we crashed at the, uh...
那個有乒乓桌的平房住了一陣
the bungalow colony with the ping-pong table.
嗯  你消失了  爸爸回來時你不在
Yeah. Uh, y-you disappeared. Dad came back. You were gone.
他送我去鮑比那兒待了幾個月
He shipped me off to Bobby's for a couple months
然后去找你
And went and found you.
你好像出去獵魔走丟了
You were lost on a hunt or something.
原來是這么跟你說的  想起來了
That's what we told you. Right.
什么意思  什么叫這么跟我說的
I'm sorry. That's what you told me?
其實呢
TRuth is, um...
我打牌把爸爸給我們買食物的錢輸光了
I lost the food money that dad left for us in a card game.
我知道你會餓肚子
I knew you'd get hungry,
所以我去當地超市里偷東西  被人抓包
so I tried taking the five-finger discount at the local market and got busted.
我根本沒去獵魔  他們送我去了個男童院
I wasn't on a hunt. They sent me to a boys' home.
那是像教養院嗎
A boys' home, like a reform school?
差不多吧
Yeah, more or less.
那是個農場  經營農場的人  桑尼
It was a farm, and the guy who ran it -- Sonny --
他挺照顧我的
He, uh -- you know, he looked after me.
桑尼知道我們是什么職業嗎
Wait. Does Sonny know what we do?
知道  他是個好人
Yeah. He's good people.
我把電話號碼給了他
I gave him the number to the bat phone,
看來他那里出了點我們能管的事
and sounds like he's got something in our wheelhouse.
所以
So...
你能行嗎  你不會太累嗎
Hey, you gonna be cool to do this, or are you too tired?
當然  我沒事
Uh, no. Yeah, I'm just, uh... I'll be fine.
大家都同意去凱茨奇爾嗎
And everybody's okay with heading out to the Catskills?
還有誰啊
I am everybody.
是啊  那好
Yeah. Right. All right.
去拿包  我們出發
Grab your stuff, and we'll head out.
迪恩
Hey, Dean...
你為什么不告訴我你去了男童院呢
I mean, why didn't you just tell me you went to a boys' home?
不知道  是爸爸的主意
I don't know. Uh, it was dad's idea.
然后就...變成了軼事了嘛
And then it just -- you know, the story became the story.
我當時才16
I was 16.
桑尼男童院
你在這兒待了兩個月  爸爸找不到你嗎
You were here for two months and dad couldn't find you?
他找到了  他馬上就找到了
Oh, no. He found me. He found me quick.
但他把我留在了這兒  因為我弄丟了錢
But he left me here 'cause I lost our money.
你才16  犯了個錯而已
You were 16. You made a mistake.
沒錯  我犯了錯誤
Yeah. I made the mistake.
我知道你在想什么  但這不能怪爸爸
Look, I know how you think. None of this was dad's fault.
二位有什么事
What can I do for you boys?
我是迪恩  這是我弟弟薩姆
I'm Dean. This is my brother, Sam.
我們是桑尼的老朋友
We're old buddies of Sonny's.
獄友嗎
Prison buddies?
不是  能轉告他我們來了嗎
No. Uh, you mind telling him that we're here?
我去找他
I'll go get him.
我才擦過地板  把你們的鞋脫下來
I just mopped this floor, so you take off those roach stompers.
桑尼坐過牢啊
Sonny's an ex-con, huh?
怎么  我們就沒犯過錯嗎
What, and we're such angels?
相信我  他做的好事比壞事多多了
Trust me, he's more than made up for it.
斯蒂文·休勒特把他抓了個正著
Steven Hewlett caught him red-handed
-在他店里偷東西  -他偷什么了
- Stealing up at his store. - So, what did he take?
花生醬和面包
Get this -- peanut butter and bread.
好吧
Okay.
他家里人呢
And how about family?
他爸爸來電話了
Well, his old man called.
他知道是怎么回事后  說讓他爛在監獄里得了
Once he found out what happened, he said let him rot in jail.
法官去釣魚了
Judge is off on a fishing trip.
他太小  不能進郡拘留所
The boy's too young to live in county.
所以我想讓他先待這兒  等提訊
So we thought it best he stay here till arraignment.
行啊
I don't see why not, man.
謝了  桑尼
Appreciate it, Sonny.
眼睛是怎么了
Where'd you get the shiner?
-你覺得好笑嗎  -我覺得你動作太慢
- You think that's funny? - I think you're slow.
-你偷襲了我  -哪有
- You sucker punched me! - You wish!
行了  比利  讓我來吧
Come on, now! Billy, I got this, buddy.
沒事的
It's all right.
你不該那么干  小子
You shouldn't do that, kid.
為什么  因為他是警察嗎
Yeah? Why? Because he's a cop?
因為你惹他生氣  他就把手銬鑰匙帶走了
Because when you make him mad, he leaves with the key.
別緊張
Eh, don't sweat it.
治安官干的嗎
Deputy do that?
你爸
What, your old man?
那你怎么弄的
Well, then, how'd you get it?
狼人
Werewolf.
好吧
Okay.
你怎么知道我不會跑
So, how do you know I won't just run away?
因為你餓了
Because you're hungry.
才不呢
No, I'm not.
那你為什么偷花生醬和面包
Well, then, why'd you steal bread and peanut butter?
這是什么地方啊
So, what is this place, anyway?
專門為你這樣的男孩準備的
It's for boys like you.
你去種地
You work the land.
我教你服從紀律  承擔責任
Teaches you some discipline and responsibility.
讓你不去惹麻煩
Keeps you out of trouble.
真無聊
That's lame.
總比監獄強
Beats jail.
來吧  我給你弄點吃的
Come on. I'll fix you something to eat.
D狗
Dee-dawg!
-桑尼  見到你真好  -你也是啊  伙計
- Sonny, good to see you. - Hey, you, too, brother.
-這一定是薩姆了  -見到你很榮幸
- Oh, and this must be Sam. - Good to meet you.
我也是  伙計
Back at you, brother.
農場看起來不錯嘛
So, farm looks, uh, nice.
得了吧  都要經營不下去了
Oh, please, man. It's barely standing.
-現在就不幾個孩子在這兒干活兒了  -為什么
- Only got a handful of kids working around here now. - Why's that?
因為如今  司法系統
Because these days, the system
寧可讓孩子去坐牢而不是改過
would rather incarcerate a boy than redeem him.
桑尼  我們能單獨談嗎
Hey, Sonny, uh, y-you mind if we talk alone?
露絲  你去看看孩子們  好嗎
Hey, Ruth, would you, uh, please go check on the boys,
確認他們在做早上的雜活兒了
make sure their morning chores are getting done?
好了  怎么回事
All right. So, what's happening?
你還記得杰克吧
Well, you remember Jack, don't you?
那個老海軍陸戰隊員硬漢
Yeah. The, uh, tough, old leatherneck.
不知怎么  那個又老又破  銹跡斑斑的拖拉機
Well, somehow, that ancient, rusty, broken-down tractor
前天晚上突然啟動把他壓死了
just roared to life and ran him over the other night.
或許就是意外
Maybe -- maybe it just, uh, slipped out of park or something.
不可能
Couldn't have.
要知道我一直不相信你們干的那些鬼鬼神神的事
You know, I never -- I never believed any of this mumbo-jumbo stuff you boys are into,
但這事有些蹊蹺
but... something ain't right.
什么意思
What do you mean?
出了一些事
Well, just things started happening --
燈忽明忽暗
You know, lights flickering on and off,
墻里有奇怪的抓撓聲
strange scratching sounds coming from inside the walls,
窗和門突然關上
windows and doors slamming.
好了  你能把孩子們召集起來嗎
All right. You think you can round up the boys
我們要到處看看
while we take a look around?
沒問題  大部分都回家休假了
Well, that shouldn't be a problem. Most are home on break --
除了一些無家可回的孩子
Well, except those with no home worth going to.
你查房子
All right. Why don't you take the house?
我去查谷倉
I'll check out the barn.
好
Yeah.
迪恩·溫
抱歉
Hey. I am so sorry.
我以為我看到了什么
I-I-I thought I... saw something in, uh --
鬼嗎
Like a ghost?
桑尼告訴我你們是老朋友
Sonny told me you were old friends,
但我知道你們是來干什么的
but I know why you're really here.
所以我在為我們祈禱
That's why I was praying for us.
祈禱什么
Praying for what?
祈禱在農場陰魂不散的鬼離開
For the ghost that haunts this farm to leave.
好吧  鬼馬小精靈
All right, Casper...
你在哪呢
Where are you at?
有人嗎
Hello?
這兒有人嗎
Anybody here?
孩子  你怎么自己在這兒
Hey, kid, what are you doing in here by yourself?
打怪獸
Fighting monsters.
什么樣的怪獸
What kind of monsters?
各種怪獸  我跟怪獸粉碎者布魯斯一起打他們
All sorts with Bruce the monster smasher.
他還穿斗篷啊
Hmm. Is that a cape?
這對打怪獸有點不太現實吧
Little impractical for smashing monsters, huh?
或許會卡住呢
You know, you could choke.
我打敗邪惡
I clobber evil!
那是當然
I bet you do.
我是迪恩
I'm Dean.
蒂米
Timmy.
我們再來一次
Let's try that again.
如果你想做個男人
If you're gonna be a man,
就得像大男人那樣握手
you got to learn how to shake like one, okay?
拿出你最好的握手來
So give me your best kung fu grip.
很好  直視我的眼睛
Good. Now look me straight in the eye.
讓我知道你不是鬧著玩的
Let me know that you mean business.
用力搖一下  這就對了
Shake as hard as you can. That's it.
這樣握手就挺好
You shake like that, you'll be all right.
蒂米  你知道在這兒工作的杰克嗎
Hey, Timmy, did you know Jack who worked here?
能跟我說說他嗎
What can you tell me about him?
他老是吼
He yelled a lot.
他出事的時候就在吼
He was yelling when he had his accident.
你怎么知道的
How do you know that?
因為事發的時候我和其他男孩在這兒玩
'cause me and the other boys were playing here when it happened.
你們看到什么了嗎
Did you see anything?
關于那晚的事
Is there anything else about that night
你還記得什么嗎
that you can remember, anything at all?
周圍突然變冷了
It suddenly got really cold.
我能走了嗎
Can I go?
我得去干活兒了  否則露絲小姐要生氣的
I have to finish my chores before Ms. Ruth gets mad.
露絲挺嚴厲的  是吧
That Ruth -- she runs a tight ship, huh?
是啊  你快去吧
Yeah, you better roll.
我是在這兒長大的
I grew up in this town.
我小時候經常來這兒
I used to come up here as a little girl.
霍華德和多琳·瓦瑟勞夫
The Wasserlaufs, Howard and Doreen --
當時農場是他們的
they used to own this farm back then.
我的同事  杰克  愿他安息
My co-worker, Jack, may he rest in peace,
他在這農場做工
he worked here as a farmhand.
霍華德是個好人
Howard was a nice man, but...
但他有酒癮
Well, he'd get into that corn liquor.
有天晚上  他不知怎么了
And one night he got it into his thick skull
就認定杰克和他妻子多琳在干草垛上做愛
that Jack and his wife, Doreen, were rolling around in the hay.
根本不是那樣的
It wasn't true, but --
但霍華德被妄想左右
But Howard's paranoia got the better of him.
他想殺了他們倆
He tried to kill them both.
杰克逃過一劫  但多琳
Jack got away, but Doreen...
他殺了她
He killed her?
用一把切肉刀
With a meat cleaver.
判了無期
Got life in jail...
霍華德一年前死了
Which for Howard ended a year ago.
他一直發誓說要報復可憐的老杰克
He always swore he'd get his revenge on poor, old Jack,
看來他終于成功了
and...looks like he finally got it.
霍華德埋在鎮上嗎
Is Howard buried here in town?
那么說
So
是爸爸不想讓你說嗎
dad didn't want you to tell me.
為什么
How come?
這里就那么糟嗎
Was this place really so bad?
我都不怎么記得了
I don't really remember.
沒人把我怎么樣
I mean, look, nobody bad touched me.
也沒人拿煙頭燒我  或是拿鐵衣架打我
Nobody burned me with their smokes or beat me with a metal hanger.
我覺得這不錯了
I call that a win.
行了  我們趕快燒了這老骨頭
All right. Let's barbecue old MacDonald here,
然后離開這里
get the hell out of dodge.
救命
Help!
露絲  你沒事吧
Ruth, you okay?
怎么了
What's wrong?
開門
Open up!
露絲
Ruth!
迪恩  你知道
Dean, you know I'm fine
我們隨便去哪買個漢堡帶走我就滿足了
just grabbing a burger to go somewhere, right?
不嘗嘗世上最好吃的香蕉煎薄餅嗎
What, and miss out on the best banana pancakes you ever had?
家庭餐館
-謝了  -不客氣
- Thanks. - No problem.
所有孩子在這兒待了一個月我都請他們來吃飯
I do this for all the boys after they've been here for a month.
我是說謝謝你幫我撤銷了對我的指控
I meant for getting the charges against me dropped.
餓不是罪
Well, being hungry's not a crime.
偷東西才是
It's the stealing that is.
我覺得如果你只干過一次
But I feel if you only do that once,
就不該留個案底
you don't deserve a record.
而且既然我們找不到你爸爸
And seeing as how we can't find your pops anywhere,
你想在這兒待多久都行  迪恩
you can stay here as long as you want, Dean.
你在學校的成績不錯  也交了朋友
You're doing good in school. You're making friends.
還進了摔跤隊
You made the wrestling team.
我很為你驕傲
I'm proud of you.
我問你
Let me ask you something,
我希望你跟我說實話
And I want you to be straight with me.
你喜歡重金屬魔鬼崇拜什么的嗎
Are you into the whole heavy-metal, devil-worshiping stuff?
什么
What?
當然不啊
No.
我沒別的意思
Hey, I'm not -- I'm not judging.
只是我看到你床柱上刻了幾個神秘的符號
It's just I found a few occult-looking symbols carved into your bedpost.
那是
It's...
說來話長
It's a very long story.
這跟你每晚睡覺前
That story have anything to do
都在屋門前撒鹽有關嗎
with why you put the salt in front of your bunk door every night before bed?
我們家就這樣  我不能說太多
Well, it's a family thing, so I can't really talk about it.
就是把你扔在這兒的家庭嗎
Same family that left you here?
你是怎么了
What are you --
你加入黑幫了還是怎么的
What are you, in the mob or something?
不是
More like something.
我曾加入過一個幫派
I was part of this gang, right?
他們就像我的家人
They were my family.
我愿為他們生  為他們死
I lived, breathed, I would have even died for them.
但你知道我落得什么下場嗎
You know where it got me?
在監獄關了15年
15 years in a correctional facility.
為了什么
And for what?
忠誠嗎  忠于誰
Being loyal? To who?
我該忠于自己的
I should have been loyal to myself.
因為人生只有一次  迪恩
Because you get one shot at this game, Dean,
你照鏡子的時候
and when you look in the mirror,
鏡子里的人應該為自己做主
you want the guy looking back at you to be his own man.
二位好啊
Hey, guys.
羅賓  你好啊
Hey, Robin. How are you?
-我挺好  你呢  -挺好的
- I'm good. How are you? - Good.
這是我的新農場工頭  迪恩
Meet my new ranch foreman here, Dean.
羅賓
歡迎光臨家庭餐館  二位來點什么
Hi. Welcome to cus's. What can I get you two?
肯定沒想到會在這兒見到我吧
Bet you never thought you'd see me here, huh?
我現在挺忙的
Uh, look, I'm a little bit slammed right now.
你們想聽聽特色菜嗎
Do you guys want to hear the specials?
羅賓  我是迪恩·溫徹斯特
Robin... Dean Winchester.
我以前住在桑尼那兒
Um... I used to live up at Sonny's.
抱歉  我就是...
Uh, look, sorry. There's just --
那里住過好多男孩
There's so many boys that pass through there,
我不可能把每個人都記住啊
It's -- it's hard to remember every -- every name and face.
是啊  抱歉  我就是...
Yeah. Uh, no. Sorry, I just --
我記得你跟你媽去農場
I remember you coming up there with your mom.
她教我們彈吉他
She'd give guitar lessons. It's, uh --
真是過了很久了
It was a long time ago.
是啊  我媽最喜歡去幫助那些男孩了
Yeah. Mom -- she loved helping out the boys.
所以她去世后  我也去給他們上課
I guess that's why I kept giving lessons after she passed.
羅賓
Hey, Robin?
失陪一下  我就回來
Um, would you excuse me? I'll be right back.
-伙計  -我們走吧
- Dude... - Let's go.
你怎么回事啊
What was that?
沒什么
Nothing.
沒什么  你顯然是有什么
Nothing? Well, obviously it was something.
那個女服務員是誰
Who was that waitress?
都說了沒什么了  別提了
Said it was nothing, all right? Drop it.
桑尼
Sonny.
什么
What?!
我努力想進去救她  門就是打不開
I tried to get in to save her, but the damn door wouldn't open.
鎖住了嗎
Locked?
農場里沒有鎖
There's no locks on the farm.
看來我們去墓地的一趟是白跑了
That means our little field trip to the cemetery was a bust.
桑尼你還記得什么其他的怪事嗎
Sonny, is there anything else weird you can remember?
現在不是已經到處是怪事了嗎
What,'cause we're not chest-deep in weird already, boys?
我知道  你再想想  什么都行
I know, I know. I mean anything -- really.
是有一件事
There was one thing.
露絲總是帶著她的串珠
Ruth always had her rosary beads with her,
但現在我找不到了
But now I can't find them anywhere.
好吧  我們先想想被害人
All right. Um, let's start with the vics, okay?
他倆都住在房子里
I mean, both lived in the house.
工作都跟這些男孩有關
They both, uh, worked closely with the boys.
我去跟那些孩子談談
All right, why don't I go have a chat with the rug rats,
看看是怎么回事
see what's up?
好
Yeah.
桑尼  你有兩名被害人的雇員記錄嗎
Sonny, you got any employee records on the victims?
在我辦公室
In my office.
走吧
Let's do it.
怎么  你要怎么辦  哭鼻子嗎
Come on, whatcha gonna do about it? You gonna cry?
蒂米  你個小怪物
Timmy, you're such a little weirdo.
你們干什么呢  給我過來
What are you doing? Come here. Huh?
沒什么
Nothing.
蒂米  怎么回事
Timmy, what's going on?
行了  你們倆
All right, you two.
露絲今早出事的時候你們在哪
Where were you this morning when Ruth had her accident?
除非你是警察  我們什么都不用跟你說
Unless you're a cop, we don't need to tell you anything.
這樣啊
Oh, okay.
瞧見沒
Well...how about that?
我們今早根本不在
We weren't even here this morning.
桑尼讓我們去鎮上買雞食  我發誓
Sonny sent us into town to get some chicken feed -- we swear.
那露絲呢  跟我說說她
What about Ruth? What can you tell me about her?
我們以前管她叫典獄長
Uh, we used to call her the warden.
她特別信奉宗教  很嚴厲
She was a real bible-thumping hard-ass.
看出來了  還有嗎
Obviously. What else?
能不能想到什么不尋常的奇怪的事
Anything different or weird you can think of?
除了蒂米嗎
You mean besides Timmy?
你們倆再敢碰他
Either of you touch him ever again,
我可就對你們動刑了
I'm gonna go all guantanamo on you.
聽懂了嗎
Understand me?
給我滾吧
Get the hell out of here.
滾啊
Go on! Get.
你和布魯斯沒事吧
You and Bruce okay?
嗯
Yeah.
聽我說
Listen to me.
他們那樣的人只是懦夫
Guys like that -- they're cowards, okay?
只要你敢勇敢面對他們一次
All you got to do is stand up to them one time
他們就再不敢欺負你了  我保證
and they'll stop, I promise.
好
Okay.
桑尼  等等
Sonny, wait.
這都是什么
Um... w-what is all this?
榮譽堂
It's our hall of fame.
我們這兒來過不少很厲害的運動員
We had some pretty great athletes come through here,
包括你哥哥
including your brother.
他曾經是蘇利文郡135磅級的摔跤冠軍
He was Sullivan county 135-pound wrestling champion.
大伙兒們好啊
Hey, guys!
她什么時候給我上課我都愿意
She could give me a lesson anytime.
惡心  她就像個老古董似的
Gross. She's like ancient.
怎么回事
What the hell?
這東西怎么會在這里
What's this doing in here?
這孩子估計得縫八千針
Kid's gonna need about 8,000 stitches,
但是他會好起來的
but he'll be fine.
那孩子在事故發生前欺負過蒂米  是吧
That kid was bullying Timmy before the accident, right?
是的  怎么了
Yeah. Why?
看看這個
Check this out.
蒂米是在一棟廢棄的建筑物里被人發現的
Timmy was found in an abandoned building
那是大約一年前  他當時孤身一人
about a year ago all by himself.
沒人確定他在那里呆了多久
No one was sure how long he had been there.
他的父母呢
And what about his parents?
他們在網上放了一張照片
Well, they posted a picture on the internet,
但是兩人都沒出現過
but no one ever showed up.
那么  他怎么會來這里
Well, then, what's he doing here?
他不是應該去孤兒院嗎
Shouldn't he be in an orphanage?
他不斷從這種機構里逃跑
He kept running away from child services.
所以大概三個月前  桑尼提出接收他
So about three months ago, Sonny offered to take him in.
好吧  所以說壞輔導員
All right, so hard-ass counselors,
小惡霸都被整了  但是蒂米卻沒事
bullies all bite the dust, but Timmy's still standing.
所以我們怎么看這件事
So, what are we talking?
我們遇上了一個達米安
We got ourselves a Damien on our hands?
《兇兆2》里的小男孩  是魔鬼的化身
不是  電磁干擾表明不是惡魔搞的鬼
No. EMF rules out a demon.
所以  八成是惡鬼附身
So... probably ghost possession.
什么意思  難不成我們要找到蒂米
Meaning what, we find Timmy and
往他喉嚨里塞一把鹽
shove a fistful of salt down his throat,
強行讓惡鬼離體
forced ejection?
這次換你去谷倉
You're taking the barn this time.
所以說  你去過很多地方
So, you've been a lot of places?
是啊  我
Yeah. My, uh...
我老爸喜歡到處走
My dad likes to move around a lot.
你爸是干什么的
What's your dad do?
都是些無聊的事
Boring stuff.
你喜歡這樣嗎
Do you like it?
不  并不喜歡
No, not really.
但是我爸想我追隨他的步伐
But my dad expects me to follow in his footsteps.
所以我差不多已經習慣了
So I've kind of gotten used to it.
是啊  我明白
Yeah. I-I get it.
我老爸想我接手這家餐廳
My pops wants me to take over the diner,
但是他不會如愿的
but that's not happening.
所以說  你自己真正想干的事是什么
So, what do you really want to do?
我想成為一個攝影師  全世界到處看看
I want to be a photographer and see the world,
去那些奇怪的地方  吃那些瘋狂的食物
go to strange lands, eat crazy food.
我想成為搖滾明星  但是
I want to be a rock star, but...
我也很喜歡汽車
I also really like cars.
當一個機械師看起來很苦啊
Being a mechanic seems rough.
什么
What?
不不  完全不會
No, no. Not at all.
汽車酷死了
Cars are freaking cool as hell.
修理他們就像解謎
Fixing them is like a puzzle,
最棒的是當你完成了你的工作
and the best part is when you're done,
他們就會離開
they leave,
然后你就再也不用為他們負責了
and you're not responsible for them anymore.
你吻過很多女孩子嗎
Have you kissed many girls?
什么
What?
是啊  當然了
Yeah. Of course.
很多
Lots.
真的
Really?
那就讓我們繼續練習練習吧
Well, I guess we'll just have to keep practicing.
在餐廳時你怎么了
Uh, what happened to you at the diner?
我轉過身去幫你點菜  但你居然走了
I turned around to take your order, and you were just gone.
說來話長  你看見蒂米了嗎
Long story. Um, have you seen Timmy?
沒啊  沒看見  但是他應該馬上就會來這兒
No, not yet, but he should be here any minute
上他的吉他課了
for his guitar lesson.
是的  我們得把今天的課取消了
Yeah, we're gonna cancel that.
什么
What?
我們得離開這里  好嗎  我沒時間解釋了
We got to get out of here, okay? I don't have time to explain.
你只要相信我就好
You just got to trust me.
相信你
T-trust you?
我為什么要再相信你一次呢
And why would I do that again?
你其實是記得我的
You do remember me.
我怎么能忘得掉
How could I forget?
怎么了
What's wrong?
我只是希望這永遠不會結束
I just hope this lasts.
我哪兒也不去  羅賓
I'm not going anywhere, Robin.
是啊  說得好聽
Yeah, says you.
我不能
Well, I can't.
否則還有誰會帶你去學校舞會呢
Who else would take you to the school dance?
這就是你邀請我
Is this your way of asking me
做你女伴的方式嗎  迪恩·溫徹斯特
to be your date, Dean winchester?
是的
Yeah.
到目前做得怎么樣
How am I doing so far?
我不得不離開  是有原因的
There were -- there were reasons why I had to leave.
現在我沒時間跟你解釋
I don't have time to explain them to you right now.
我得把你帶離這里
I got to get you out of here.
你在干什么
What are you doing?!
對不起
I'm sorry.
為什么對不起  蒂米
Sorry about what, Timmy?
我無法阻止
I can't stop it.
走走走
Go, go, go!
薩姆  快走
Sam, go!
-鎖上了  -該死
- Locked. - Damn it!
畫圈
Circle.
迪恩  剛剛那是怎么回事
Dean, what -- what just happened in there?
聽我說
Okay, listen to me.
不管發生什么  你都不要出這個圈
Whatever happens, you stay inside this circle.
明白嗎
Understood?
好了  迪恩
All right. Dean...
我沒法控制她
I can't control her.
不能控制誰
Can't control who?
你媽媽  對嗎
Your mom, right?
蒂米  聽著
Timmy, listen.
你得告訴我們著火的事情  好嗎
We need you to tell us about the fire, okay?
當時很晚了  我們開車回家
It was late, and we were driving home
在樹林里撞車了
when we crashed in the woods.
全都著火了
Everything was on fire.
但是她救了我
But she saved me,
在車爆炸前
pushed me out...
把我推了出去
before the car blew up...
她卻還在車里
with her in it.
但并不只是如此  對嗎
But that's not all, was it?
我跑著穿過森林
I ran through the woods.
找到了一個空建筑  躲在里面
I found an empty building, where I hid.
我很害怕
I was scared.
又黑又冷  所以我就哭了
It was dark and cold. So I cried.
我哭著叫媽媽
I cried for my mom.
然后她就出現了
And then she came.
但是她變了  是嗎
But she had changed, right?
我敢說那個帥氣的玩具小人就是她給你的  對嗎
I'll bet she gave you that cool action figure, huh?
對  我9歲的時候
Yeah. When I turned 9.
蒂米
Timmy...
你需要把那個玩具小人給我
...I'm gonna need that action figure.
不
No!
我打敗邪惡
I clobber evil!
I...clobber...evil!
似乎不是玩具小人
It looks like it wasn't the action figure
把她束縛在這里的  迪恩
that was anchoring her here, Dean.
那是什么呢
Well, then, what is?!
他
Him.
你知道嗎
You know what?
我覺得也許他媽媽不能放手
I think maybe his mom can't let go
她還在墳墓中保護著他
and she's still protecting him from the grave.
保護他什么  保護他不被我們傷害嗎
Protecting him from what? What, from us?
也許她不知道哪些威脅是真實的哪些不是
Maybe she doesn't know what threats are real and what's not,
所以她就一起攻擊了
so she just attacks all of them.
好極了  除非我們廢了那孩子
Great. So, what, unless we waste the kid,
否則我們就會一直被攻擊
we're sitting ducks?
這太瘋狂了
This is -- this is crazy.
羅賓  羅賓
Robin. Robin!
該死
Damn it.
羅賓  等等
Robin, wait!
你到底是誰
Who are you?
現在我是唯一能確保你安全的人
Right now I'm the only thing that's keeping you safe.
蒂米  我們需要你的幫忙  好嗎
Timmy, we're gonna need your help, okay?
聽我說  我需要你集中注意力
Listen to me. I need you to focus, okay?
我們不是來傷害你的
Look, we are not here to hurt you.
小薩姆
Sammy!
我不能阻止她
I can't stop her.
蒂米  你得試一試
Timmy, you have to try!
她在你需要她的時候找到了你
She came to you when you cried out for her.
現在你得告訴她住手然后走開
Now you have to tell her to stop and go away!
-她是我媽媽  -她是一個鬼魂
- She's my mom. - She's a ghost.
蒂米  因為她不能繼續前進  所以越來越瘋狂
Timmy, because she can't move on, she's going crazy.
你得放她走  你不會有事的
Okay? You got to let her go. You'll be okay.
聽我說
Listen to me.
有時你得做一些對你最好的事情
Sometimes you got to do what's best for you,
即使會傷害你所愛的人
even if it's gonna hurt the ones you love.
媽咪
Mommy...
住手
Stop it.
蒂米  像個大人那樣
Timmy, kung-fu grip!
媽咪  住手  不要再傷害別人了
Mommy, stop it! Stop hurting people!
你得離開  永遠不要回來
You have to go. Never come back.
我會沒事的  我保證
I'll be okay. I promise.
我也愛你
I love you, too.
那么這是家族事業嗎
So, then, this is the family business?
跟你說了這很無趣的
Told you it was boring.
是啊
Yeah, right.
如你所見
Well, as you can see,
我沒有逃走變成搖滾明星
I did not run off to become a rock star.
這我就不知道了呢
Mm... I don't know about that.
對我來說你很帥呢  迪恩·溫徹斯特
You look pretty rockin' to me, Dean Winchester.
你呢
And what about you?
我一直在想
I mean, I always thought
我會討厭一輩子都待在這一個小鎮上
that I would hate being in the same little town my whole life,
正如我爸希望的那樣  接管餐廳
and, you know, taking over the diner like dad always wanted,
但是  我真的不討厭
but...I don't.
我很喜歡
I just -- I love it.
我想我們還是不能理解16歲時一切的想法啊
I guess we didn't know everything we thought we did at 16, huh?
不是一切
Not everything.
只是一部分而已
Just some things.
聽起來蒂米需要別人幫助他調整一下
Sounds like Timmy's gonna need some help adjusting.
沒錯  但他還有你
Yeah, but he's got you.
我真的很不喜歡看著你離開  D狗
I always hate to see you go, Dee-dawg.
這次真的太感謝你們了
Can't thank you enough for this one, man.
桑尼  回見吧
Sonny, we'll see you around.
肯定的  孩子們
You can bet on that, boys.
慢慢來
Take it easy, man.
你是怎么知道
Hey, h-how did you know
蒂米讓他媽媽離開會管用
Timmy asking his mom to leave was gonna work?
不知道  絕對是碰運氣  還好碰對了
I didn't. Total Hail Mary. Got lucky.
只是碰運氣
You just got lucky?
和你在這里做的事情很像呢
Kind of like you did with this place.
我之前在想
I mean, here I was thinking
這是你生命中最糟糕的一段時間
this was the worst part of your life,
結果卻是你最好的時光
and it turns out it was the best.
你為什么離開
Why'd you ever leave?
感覺不對
Never felt right.
真的嗎
Really?
只是兩個月  薩姆  好嗎
It was two months, Sam, okay,
迫不及待想要離開這里
and I couldn't wait to get out of here.
我不知道該怎么跟你說  那不是我
I don't know what to tell you. It wasn't me.
瞧瞧你
Oh, look at you.
-你收拾好了  -謝謝你
- You clean up good! - Thank you.
你知道  我其實從來沒
You know, uh... I've never actually been
去過什么學校舞會
to one of these school dances before.
是啊
Yeah.
那個嘛  迪恩  你爸爸在外面
Look, about that, Dean, your old man's outside,
他真的很了不起
and, man, he's really something.
我試圖告訴他今晚對你來說很重要  迪恩
I tried to tell him what a big night it was for you, Dean,
問他能不能晚點再來
and ask him if he could come back later,
但他讓我告訴你  他有活兒
but he just said to tell you he had a job,
他說你知道什么意思
said you'd know what that means.
在我從監獄里出來之后
You know, after I got out of jail,
這地方給了我第二次機會
this place gave me a second chance,
對你也是一樣
and it's done the same for you, too.
如果你需要  我會為你竭力爭取
So if you want, I'll stick my neck out for you,
爭取讓你留下
and I'll fight for you to stay.
桑尼
Sonny...
謝謝你所做的一切
...thank you -- for everything.
但我得走了
But I have to go.
迪恩
Dean...
謝謝你
Thank you.
為什么
For what?
一直在這里  一直支持我
For always being there, for having my back.
我知道一直都不容易
Look, I know it always hasn't been easy.
我不知道你在說什么鬼話
I don't know what the hell you're talking about.